

TAVAHEN

Sales Representative

About Me

Experienced sales pro with a successful track record in IT, telecom, and music industries.

Specializes in technical sales, builds strong client relationships, and drives business growth.



+46 70-019 44 20



maxtavahen@gmail.com



Dag Hammarskjölds torg 9. 211 18 Malmö

LANGUAGE

- English
- Swedish

EXPERTISE

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

EXPERIENCE

HIP United AB

Sales Representative

2021 - now

Proficient in technical sales and international exporting, adeptly acting as a skilled sales representative to ensure seamless transactions between suppliers and clients.

Level Music

A&R Consultant

1997 - 2019

Experienced music professional with a successful career collaborating with multinational record labels and music publishers. Impressive track record of selling multi-platinum and gold records, showcasing sales excellence in the music industry.

Mubito AB

Founder | Manager

2004 - 2009

An innovative IT company with up to 70 employees, excelling in B2B sales. My role involved driving sales and fostering innovation. I focused on cutting-edge marketing and online sales strategies, which significantly increased visibility, conversion rates, and revenue.

EDUCATION

TUC Sweden

Corporate Sales B2B 2-year vocational college education with a degree in Business-to-Business (B2B) Sales.

- Sales concept in its entirety
- Negotiation and trust-building
- Project management, finance, and business law

Handelsakademin

1-year vocational education E-Business Management

- Digital Sales
- Marketing
- Communication
- Analysis within the realm of digital commerce